## **Riny Yadav**

Noida, Uttar Pradesh • +91 6393 103 784 • workwithriny@gmail.com • linkedin.com/in/riny-yadav-a24a90238 • https://rinyyadav313.wixsite.com/mysite

## **UI/UX DESIGNER**

I'm a graphic designer with a year of experience. My passion is creating user-friendly designs that are both visually appealing and functional. You can explore my portfolio to get an idea of the kind of projects I have worked on. I look forward to the opportunity to work with you and help bring your ideas to life. I'm an organized and dependable candidate successful at managing multiple priorities with a positive attitude. Willingness to take on added responsibilities to meet team goals.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## Status Anxiety • 01/2023 - 03/2024 Graphic Designer

- · Social media content creation.
- Collaborated with design teams to design, test, integrate new graphic concepts and interfaces.
- Identified and resolved flaws, conducted user research and analysis, proposed new original ideas on how the user experience could be improved.

# Bitcs · Noida · 01/2022 - 12/2023

- Managing all HR-Related tasks along with a team, including documentation, interviewing, training and onboarding new recruits.
- Sourcing candidates through different platforms and managing end to end Hiring.

### **EDUCATION**

Guru Gobind Singh Indraprastha University • 01/2019 - 12/2022

#### SKILLS

Adobe photoshop, Graphic design, Illustrator, Image editing, Indesign, Logo design, Project coordination, UI/UX Design, Visual design, Website Design